Subscribe to the Bankbajar.com
channel and press the bell button
to watch the video first Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
bankbajar.com Friends, if you have an
account in IDFC Bank, then watch this video
carefully. In this video, we will
tell you important information related to that bank account.
Today, we will tell you
how you can activate its mobile application in your mobile and
how you can use it. So
friends, let's start the video. First of all, to
download the mobile application, you have to
go to the Play Store and type
Mobile ICICI Bank. As soon as you type,
you will see the option that appears and you will
download this application by using it. So, to
install the mobile application,
your registered SIM should be installed in this mobile
and your ATM card
and the PIN of the ATM card should also be created.
Let's see that our application has been
downloaded here, so we have to
open it by simply clicking on Open.
As soon as we click on the Open button, we will
see that this application is opening here
and here, as soon as the
loading is complete, you will
see that the next option will come to you.
You will click on 'Already have an account'
and you will set it daily.
You will see in the next window that you will see the 'Activate' button here. You
will activate your application by clicking on it to
activate it with your registered number.
You will have to verify your mobile number here, by
clicking on which you will verify it. As soon as it is
verified, you will be
shown 3 options on the next page, in which
you will see in the first option that you can
create a four digit PIN with your finger print.
In the second option,
you can create a four colour PIN without finger print.
In the third, if you have internet
banking and user ID, then you can
login directly from here. So let's
create a four digit PIN.
Look, we have created a four digit PIN here and
clicked on the submit button and it has been
successfully generated here.
Now you will go to the next step, here you will
see that on the back of your ATM card,
you will see some flat
numbers in ABCD form. You have to fill those numbers
with your card,
like here the option of CHP is coming,
so you can enter your ATM card.  See this code from behind,
enter it here and
click on the activate button. Now you
will see that in the next step, it is
asking you to enter your ATM card PIN. So, enter
your ATM card PIN and
authorize it and
submit it. Friends, as soon as this is submitted,
your application has been installed from here
and you will be given a message that
your mobile application has been installed. If you
want to enable fingerprint in the application, then an option is available here.
Click on it and enable this application.
This will benefit you in that you will
not need to remember the PIN again and again.
You will open this application through your fingerprint only. So
friends, the
mobile application has been completely installed
and activated here. So, we will
tell you further how you will be able to use it. So
friends, for this, we will
login to our application from here.
You can also login here with your fingerprint
or you can login by entering a four-digit PIN. So, let's
log in with the fingerprint.
Friends, the
home page of the mobile has opened here where you will
see one and a half options.  If it is giving then you
will see that here there is fund transfer, bill,
recharge, Mi, this is the account and you go to the next page and turn around,
here you will see the option of star deposit,
iBank option is coming
and after that on the next page you will see that
here you can book train tickets, flight
tickets and you
can use many options here, friends, that's all
for today, we will meet you soon in the
next video, in this we will
tell you in detail that by using iMobile application
you can avail other facilities
and how you
can login to internet banking and use it, so
friends, for this you should subscribe to this channel
and press the bell button so
that you keep getting notifications of every upcoming video
and friends,
if you liked this video then like this video
and share it with your friends, if
you need any more information related to iA mobile
or need any help then you
can comment or mail us,
we have given you the information in the description box,
thank you.